http://www.fineartstore.com/t-privacy.aspx

Wish List
Your Account
Login
Your Basket (0 items)
Easels, Furniture, & Lighting
Everyday Is Black Friday!
DAS
Daylight Corp.
Hahnemuhle
Hand Book Paper Co.
Legion Paper
Leo Uhlfelder Co.
Royal Brush
Royal Sovereign Ltd.
Wolff's Pencil
Worldwide Co.
Easels, Furniture, & Lighting
Everyday Is Black Friday!
Miscellaneous
Best SellersNew ProductsFeatured ProductsSpecial OffersGift Ideas
Hahnemuhle
Hand Book Paper Co.
LascauxLegion Paper
Leo Uhlfelder Co.
Royal Brush
Royal Sovereign Ltd.
Wolff's Pencil
Worldwide Co.
Easels, Furniture, & Lighting
Everyday Is Black Friday!
Privacy Policy
Fine Art Store is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy applies to the Fine Art Store Web site and governs data collection and usage. By using the Fine Art Store website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.
Collection of your Personal Information
Fine Art Store collects personally identifiable information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address or telephone number. Fine Art Store also collects anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your ZIP code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites.
There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by Fine Art Store. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring Web site addresses. This information is used by Fine Art Store for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Fine Art Store Web site.
Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through Fine Art Store public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others. Note: Fine Art Store does not read any of your private online communications.
Fine Art Store encourages you to review the privacy statements of Web sites you choose to link to from Fine Art Store so that you can understand how those Web sites collect, use and share your information. Fine Art Store is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on Web sites outside of the Fine Art Store and Fine Art Store family of Web sites.
Use of your Personal Information
Fine Art Store collects and uses your personal information to operate the Fine Art Store Web site and deliver the services you have requested. Fine Art Store also uses your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Fine Art Store and its affiliates. Fine Art Store may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.
Fine Art Store does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. Fine Art Store may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. In addition, Fine Art Store may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Fine Art Store, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.
Fine Art Store does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.
Fine Art Store keeps track of the Web sites and pages our customers visit within Fine Art Store, in order to determine what Fine Art Store services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within Fine Art Store to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.
Fine Art Store Web sites will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Fine Art Store or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Fine Art Store; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Fine Art Store, or the public.
Use of Cookies
The Fine Art Store Web site use "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.
One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Fine Art Store pages, or register with Fine Art Store site or services, a cookie helps Fine Art Store to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same Fine Art Store Web site, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Fine Art Store features that you customized.
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Fine Art Store services or Web sites you visit.
Security of your Personal Information
Fine Art Store secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. Fine Art Store secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other Web sites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.
Changes to this Statement
Fine Art Store will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. Fine Art Store encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Fine Art Store is protecting your information.
Contact Information
Fine Art Store welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Fine Art Store has not adhered to this Statement, please contact Fine Art Store at customerservice@fineartstore.com. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
Be in the Know
Blog
Explore our tutorial videos
Gallery
Need Help?
Copyright © fineartstore.com   |  Powered by equaTEK Interactive
